JAMES V. KEEFE, JR.

Dover, NH 03820 Open to Remote Work (603) 534-8506) jvkeefe@gmail.com www.github.com/jkeefe77

SUMMARY Former police officer turned web developer. Experienced in building customized web pages and applications for both web and mobile development. Active listener and effective communicator with analytical skills that allow for the design of responsive apps with the customer's vision always in focus. Adaptable, focused, and capable of managing complex tasks to meet any deadline.

EDUCATION SUFFOLK UNIVERSITY Boston, MA

September 2003- April 2007

Bachelor of Arts, Sociology

CAREER FOUNDRY

April 2023- present

Full Stack web developer certification (in progress)

SKILLS CODING LANGUAGES / SPECIALTIES

- Full Stack web development (MERN)
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, SQL
- Git, GitHub, Git Bash, cloud computing.

EXPERIENCE

CITY OF DOVER Dover, NH

April 2016 - March 2023

TOWN OF FARMINGTON Farmington, NH

Police Officer

- Trained and evaluated recruits as a Field Training Officer
- Conducted thorough investigations while responding to calls for service
- Processed evidence as member of Crime Scene Unit

PARADIGM PRECISION Malden, MA

March 2012 - April 2016

Material Coordinator/ Buyer

- Coordinated material movement between internal teams and outside suppliers
- Negotiated with suppliers for optimal pricing and conditions
- Managed costs as part of the procurement process with supply chain management